Guide to the George Sherwood Eddy Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
George Sherwood Eddy Papers
1851-1981
RG 32
Yale University Divinity School Library
10
(24 boxes)
The collection consists of correspondence, writings, collected material, personal items, and memorabilia that document the activities and associations of George Sherwood Eddy throughout his career as a YMCA secretary, seminar leader, author, lecturer, and evangelist. George Sherwood Eddy was born in Leavenworth, Kansas on January 19, 1871. He earned a Ph.B. degree from Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University in 1891, attended Union Theological Seminary and graduated from Princeton Theological Seminary. Eddy worked for the YMCA, Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions, and American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions. He was appointed YMCA secretary for Asia in 1911. Eddy wrote and published numerous books and pamphlets from 1895-1955. He died in Jacksonville, Illinois on November 4, 1963.
Eddy, Sherwood, 1871-1963
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
1871, January 19 Born Leavenworth, Kansas, son of George Alfred and Margaret Louise Norton Eddy
1887, 1888 Preparatory School at Phillips-Andover Academy, Massachusetts
1891 Ph.B. Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University
1891 -1896 Worked for Y.M.C.A. and Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions in New York City; Attended Union Theological Seminary; Graduated from Princeton Theological Seminary
1896-1911 Worked in India under auspices of the International Committee of the Y.M.C.A. and the American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions; Traveling Secretary for the S.V.M. in India and Ceylon; While visiting in India, Eddy's mother organized the Kodaikanal School
1898, November 10 Married Alice Maud Harriet Arden (1873-1945) - Children: Margaret M. (d. 1932); Arden (d. 1917)
1907 Attended Tokyo Conference of the World Student Christian Federation
1911 Appointed Y.M.C.A. Secretary for Asia; Worked with students of Japan, Karea, China, India, the Near East and Russia--an honorary worker without salary; Addressed Chinese provincial parliaments and boards of government institutions.
1912, 1913 Held evangelistic meetings with John R. Mott throughout Asia
1915-1917 Y.M.C.A. Secretary working with British and American armies in France during World War I
1916 M.A. (Honorary) LL.D. College of Wooster; M.A. (Honorary) Yale
1921-1957 Led traveling seminars to England and the continent; more than 1500 American leaders participated
1931 Retired from the Y.M.C.A.
1936 Aided in organization of the interracial Delta Cooperative Farms in Mississippi
1946 Married Catherine Louise Gates
1949 Moved to Jacksonville, Illinois; Taught at Illinois College and MacMurray College
1895-1955 Wrote and published numerous books and pamphlets including God in History (1947), You Will Survive After Death (1950), and his autobiography, Eighty Adventurous Years (1955).
1963, November 4 Died Jacksonville, Illinois
Biographical information taken from: Who Was Who in America, Volume IV 1961-1968, Sherwood Eddy, Eighty Adventurous Years, and Biographical Documentation, Series IV
Scope and Contents
I. Correspondence, 1912-1977, n.d.
II. Writings, 1893-1956, n.d.
III. Collected Material, 1913-1958, n.d.
IV. Personal Items and Memorabilia, 1851-1981, n.d.
These papers, dating from 1851 to 1981, document the activities and associations of Sherwood Eddy throughout his long career as a Y.M.C.A. secretary, seminar leader, author, and lecturer. Eddy's insightful letters and writings reveal much about his interests and involvements, which ranged from Christian evangelism to world politics to cooperative farms in the South to spiritualism. The controversies that accompanied Eddy's liberal views on various issues are documented.
The Eddy Papers complement numerous other collections at the Yale Divinity School Library, including the John R. Mott Papers and the archives of the Student Volunteer Movement and World Student Christian Federation. Of particular interest to the YDSL focus on China missions are the documentation of Eddy's evangelistic meetings in Asia 1911 to 1914 and letters that report on visits to China throughout the 1920s and 20s, revealing Eddy's evolving estimation of China's leadership.
The Eddy Papers came to the Library in three nearly equal sections, one during Eddy's lifetime, one donated by Eddy's widow in 1977 and one following her death in 1982. The original group of papers plus the 1977 addendum have been reorganized and integrated with the third increment.
CORRESPONDENCE, the first series, is divided into six sections:
a. Correspondence: Family. These letters, dating from 1912 to 1946, read as a travelogue telling of Eddy's activities and encounters with notable personages such as the Archbishop of Canterbury, Lloyd George, Sun Yat-sen and John R. Mott. Many of the letters exchanged between GSE and his brother, D. Brewer Eddy, deal with management of the financial resources which allowed Eddy to pursue his independent activities.
b. Correspondence: General. These letters date from 1906 to 1963. Notable correspondents include Reinhold Niebuhr, Kenneth Scott Latourette, Kirby Page, Nels F. S. Ferre', G. Bromley Oxnam, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Henry P. Van Dusen and representatives of the Student Volunteer Movement. Eddy's activities overseas are described as well as his efforts to finance various projects and arrangements for speaking engagements and publications. Letters related to the formation and development of the interracial Delta Cooperative farms in Mississippi are of particular interest.
c. Correspondence: Report Letters. These are circular type letters written from around the world.
d. Correspondence: Seventieth Birthday. A bound volume of congratulatory letters from his friends was presented to Eddy on his seventieth birthday, January 19, 1941. There are letters in this bound volume from many of the individuals who appear in the Correspondence: General section.
e. Correspondence: Kirby Page. The letters in this section, primarily written in 1953, came in response to Kirby Page's appeal to friends and acquaintances of Eddy for any material that would aid in his efforts to write a biography of Eddy. Eddy's personality and the lasting impressions he made on people are evident in these letters.
f. Correspondence of others. These are letters of Eddy family members which are neither to nor from GSE. The majority of the letters are those of Eddy's second wife, Louise Gates Eddy. A sampling of condolence letters written to her after the death of GSE has been retained as well as correspondence which relates to the symposium honoring GSE in October and the deposit of GSE's papers in the Yale Divinity School Library.
The Writings of the second series are divided into five sections:
a. Writings: Articles and Speeches. This section includes published and unpublished articles, papers,and speeches dating from 1896 to 1956. The listing of titles reveals the wide range of Eddy's interests - from world affairs to race relations to personal belief.
b. Writings: Pamphlets. These publications in pamphlet format date from 1893 to 1942 and address many of the same topics as Eddy's articles and speeches.
c. Writings: Related to Major Works. This section contains primarily drafts, notes and correspondence related Eddy's booklength works, both published and unpublished. Many of the drafts are for books written late in Eddy's life for which he was not able to find a publisher. 0f particular interest are the source materials and the notes for Eddy's book You Will Survive After Death.
d. Writings: Notes and Fragments. These more ephemeral writings and notes of Eddy are topically arranged and date from 1926 to 1955, n.d.
e. Writings: Published Works. Included in this section are noncirculating copies of Eddy's major works, both pamphlets and books. Most of these works also appear in the Library's cataloged collection.
The Collected Material of Series III is a compendium of articles, books, and pamphlets on a variety of topics that Eddy had retained in his files. The wide range of Eddy's interests is reflected here as elsewhere in his papers.
Series IV, Personal Items and Memorabilia, is divided into four sections:
a. Biographical Documentation. This section contains a wide variety of primarily printed material documenting Eddy's life and background. Articles and tributes written about Eddy are included as well as a few autobiographical writings.
b. Material Related to Seminars and Lectures. Announcements, programs, newspaper articles and other items dating from 1919 to 1958 document Eddy's seminar trips to Europe and his activities as a lecturer and evangelist in the Untied States and abroad. In 2007, additional materials related to the 1938 European Seminar were donated by John M. and Sharon D. Ewing. These consist of a VCR copy of an 8mm film taken by Joseph S. Ewing during the Seminar, a DVD made from the film footage, with audio voice-over by John M. and Sharon D. Ewing from the original journals of Ewing, the roster of participants in the Seminar and a photocopy of a photograph of the participants.
c. Financial Records. The records in this section are not comprehensive but they do provide a glimpse of the financial arrangements that allowed Eddy to be largely independent of a salary throughout his career. Finances were also a frequent topic in letters exchanged between Eddy and his brother. (see Series I)
d. Genealogical Material. These materials collected by Eddy do not document his personal family history in any detailed way.
e. Photographs. Most interesting in this section are the early photographs from China that document meetings led by Eddy in 1913 and 1914.
Arrangement
I. Correspondence, 1912-1977, n.d.
II. Writings, 1893-1956, n.d.
III. Collected Material, 1913-1958, n.d.
IV. Personal Items and Memorabilia, 1851-1981, n.d.
Missions -- China; Missions -- India; Spiritualism; Young Men's Christian Associations; Authors; Evangelists; Missionaries; Eddy, Sherwood, 1871-1963; Ford, Arthur A.; Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1892-1971; Page, Kirby, 1890-1957; Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (John Davison), 1874-1960; Van Dusen, Henry P. (Henry Pitney), 1897-1975; Wu, Yaozong, 1893-1979; Delta Cooperative Farms; Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions
- Correspondence, Series I
  Scope and Contents
  This series is divided into six sections:
  Correspondence: Family: The letters are arranged chronologically.
  Correspondence: General: The letters are arranged chronologically. The names of notable correspondents are listed for each folder.
  Correspondence: Report Letters: The letters are arranged chronologically. Folder headings also indicate the country or continent from which they were written.
  Correspondence: Seventieth Birthday: This is a bound volume of letters. No effort has been made to cross-reference correspondents who appear alphabetically within this volume.
  Correspondence: Kirby Page: These letters received by Page are arranged alphabetically by author. Some prominent correspondents are noted.
  Correspondence of others: Letters to and from four Eddy family members are separated and arranged chronologically.
  - Correspondence: Family
    - GSE to: mother, 1912-1914 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - To: mother, son, wife, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - To: mother, brother, daughter, wife, 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - To/from: brother, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - To/from: mother, brother, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - To/from: brother, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - To/from: brother, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - To/from: mother, brother, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - To/from: brother, 1927,1928 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - To/from: mother, brother, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - To/from: mother, brother, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - To/from: mother, brother, 1931 Jan-May (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - To/from: mother, brother, 1931 Jun-Dec (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - To/from: brother, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - To/from: brother, "family", 1933 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - To/from: brother, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - To/from: brother, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - To/from: brother, "folks", 1936 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - To/from: brother, "family", 1937,1939 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - To/from: brother, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - To/from: mother, brother; fragments, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: General
    - GSE to/from: Fennell P. Turner; Student Volunteer Movement, 1906-1907 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - To/from: Fennell P. Turner; Student Volunteer Movement, 1908-1912 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - To/from: Fennell P. Turner; Student Volunteer Movement, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - To/from; Fennell P. Turner; Student Volunteer Movement; Frank Buchman; Ned Carter, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - To/from: Student Volunteer Movement; Fennell P. Turner; Robert P. Wilder; Samuel N. Shoemaker, Jr., 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - To/from: Robert P. Wilder; Student Volunteer Movement; Huntley Dupre (incl. re Czechoslovak Students Renaissance Movement); Henry Timken; Kirby Page, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - To/from: James H. Lockhart; James N. Gamble; James H. Causey; William Volker; Henry Ford: Student Volunteer Movement, 1922-1923 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Incl. to/from: John D. Rockefeller, Jr.; Student Volunteer Movement; YMCA International Committee; James H. Causey; Henry Ford; Robert P. Wilder, 1924-1926 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Re Speaking schedule cancelled in North Carolina To/from: Student Volunteer Movement; Frank C. Laubach, 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - To/from: Student Volunteer Movement; James H. Lockhart; M. I. Kalinin; Raymond Robbins; Lord Irwin (Halifax); Will Danforth, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Incl. to/from: Student Volunteer Movement; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.; James H. Lockhart; H. H. Kung, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Incl. to/from: Josef Stalin; George H. Shepherd; Stanley Jones, 1932,1934 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Incl. re Sherwood Eddy Fund, 1936-1940 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Incl. to Reinhold Niebuhr and D. B. Eddy re biography of GSE, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Incl. to/from: American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions; Franz Stefan; Y. T. Wu; re Bishop Azariah Memorial Fund, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Incl. re Ahmednagar College to/from: Philip C. Jessup, 1947,1949 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Incl. from Homer C. Ling, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Incl. to/from: Reinhold Niebuhr; Norman Thomas; G. Bromley Oxnam; J. J. Mallon; Wm. Scarlett; Raymond P. Morris (YDSL); Liston Pope, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Incl. to/from: Eugene Barnett; Wm. Scarlett; Reinhold Niebuhr; Patrick M. Malin; Mladen Soich, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Incl. to/from: Mladen Soich, 1953 Jan-Mar (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Incl. to/from: Mladen Soich; Deane Ferm; Kenneth S. Latourette; Nels F. S. Ferrer G. Bromley Oxnam; S. C. Leung, 1953 Jul-1954 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Incl. to/from: Edward H. Hume; Edwin C. Lobenstine; Jerome Davis; Raymond Morris; Upton Sinclair; Kenneth S. Latourette, 1955 Jan-Feb (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Incl. to/from: Charles Ranson; Eleanor Roosevelt Charles P. Taft; Wm. Scarlett; Jerome Davis; Paul H. Douglas, 1955 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Incl. to/from: Herbert Popley; E. Stanley Jones; John Foster Dulles; Henry P. VanDusen, 1955 May-Dec (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Incl. to/from: Arthur Ford; William Ernest Hocking; J. J. Mallon, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Incl. to/from: G. Bromley Oxnam; Raymond Morris; Reinhold Niebuhr, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Incl. to/from: ABCFM; Henry P. VanDusen; Eugene Barnett; J. J. Mallon; Jerome Davis; J. B. Tito, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Incl. to/from: Henry P. VanDusen; R. Niebuhr, 1962-1963, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence: Report Letters
    - From India, 1897 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - From India, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - From India; incl. from "Yale Missionary Band - New Haven, Conn.", 1899 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - From India, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - From India, 1901 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - From India, 1902 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - From India, 1903 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - From India; incl. a trip to Burma, 1906 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - "A Trip to Japan", 1907 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - "First Impressions of the Philippines" "In Korea", 1911 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - From Russia and India, 1912 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - From Ceylon, China, Japan, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - From China, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - From India and China, 1915,1916 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - From France; incl. re death of son, Arden, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - From China, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Incl. from India, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Incl. from Europe, Egypt, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - From Japan, China, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - From Europe and Asia, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Incl. from U.S.A., 1924 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - From Europe, U.S.A., 1925 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - From U.S.A., Russia, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - From U.S.A., England, Europe, 1927 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - From England, Europe, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Incl. from Russia, Turkey, India, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - From Asia, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - From Manchuria, China, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - From China, France, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - From Germany, Russia, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - From Finland, Italy, China, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Incl. from England, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - From U.S.A., 1936 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - From U.S.A., Russia, 1937,1939 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - From U.S.A., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - From U.S.A., 1951 -1957 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence: Seventieth Birthday
    - Bound book: "To Sherwood Eddy from his friends on his Seventieth Birthday, January 19, 1941 ", 1940,1941 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence: Kirby Page
    - Re. KP's biography of GSE (A-C); incl. S. M. Cavert, H. S. Coffin, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Re. KP's biography of GSE (D-H); incl. Paul H. Douglas, Paul Harris, Sherwood Eddy, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Re. KP's biography of GSE (J-P); incl. Henry Smith Leiper, John R. Mott, Reinhold Niebuhr, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Re. KP's biography of GSE (R-Z); incl. Upton Sinclair, Norman Thomas, H. P. VanDusen, L. A. Weigle, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Re. KP's biography of GSE (first names and unidentified signatures) Correspondence of others, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence of others
    - D. Brewer Eddy, 1922-1946 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Maud Eddy to/from Fennell P. Turner, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Louise Gates Eddy from Reinhold Niebuhr, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Louise Gates Eddy: condolences, 1963 Mar (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Louise Gates Eddy: condolences and re. GSE Symposium, 1963 Apr-Jul (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Louise Gates Eddy: re. GSE Symposium, 1963 Aug-Dec (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Louise Gates Eddy: incl. to/from YMCA Historical Library; Arthur Ford; Yale Divinity School Library, 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Louise Gates Eddy: incl. to/from Deane Ferm; Yale Divinity School Library, 1971 -1976 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Louise Gates Eddy: incl. to/from Yale Divinity School Library, 1977, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Arden Kerry Smith, 1961 -1963 (Box 5, Folder 100)
- Writings, Series II
  This series is divided into five sections:
  Writings: Articles and Speeches: The articles, papers, speeches and sermons are arranged chronologically with titles noted.
  Writings: Pamphlets: The pamphlets are arranged chronologically with titles noted.
  Writings: Related to Major Works:This material is arranged in a general chronological sequence according to the date of publication or completion for each major work.
  Writings: Notes and Fragments. This material is arranged alphabetically by topic.
  Writings: Published Works. These noncirculating copies of Eddy's works are arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Writings: Articles and Speeches
    - "Ship Wrecked'', 1896 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - "Seeking to Reach the Educated Hindus", 1903 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - "Signs of Promise in India", 1904 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - "The Unoccupied Fields of India", 1905 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - "In the Tiger Jungle", 1905 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - "A National Church for India", 1912 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - "In Travancore", 1919 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - "A Nation Reborn", 1920 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - "In Cairo", 1920 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - "Czecho-Slovakia", 1920 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - "The First Student Conference in Czecho-Slovakia", 1921 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - "China's Christian General", 1922 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - "In South China", 1922 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - "The New Korea", 1922 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - "The Rebirth of Japan", 1922 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - "Gandhi - An Interpretation", 1923 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - "In Manchuria", "Now It Must Be Told", 1923 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - "Personal Observations in the Ruhr", 1923 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - "Politics in Palestine", 1923 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - "Will India Become Christian", 1923 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - "Can Jennings Work Another Miracle?", 1925 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - "The New Map of Europe", 1925 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - "The Present World Situation", 1925 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - "Stranger than Fiction", 1925 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - "The Worst Government in the World", 1925 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - "Russia, the Land of Contradictions", 1926 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - "Russia Revisited", 1926 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - "The American Legion and Free Speech", 1927 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - "Political Movements in India.. .", 1927 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - "Why I Believe in Foreign Missions", 1928 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - "Why Missions?", 1928 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - "Sherwood Eddy and Free Speech", 1928 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - "Soviet Russia as Seen Today", 1929 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - "An Interview with the Grand Mufti of Palestine", 1929 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - "British Will Lose India.. .", 1930 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - "India at the Crossroads", 1930 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - "India in Transition", 1930 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - "Japan's Policy in Korea", 1930 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - "Reconciliation or Revolution in India", 1930 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - "What A World Journey Revealed", 1930 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - "Breakfast with Karl Barth", 1935 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - "Russia - Good and Evil", 1935 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - "Lawless Arkansas", 1936 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - "A Four-fold Plan for India", 1942 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - "The Eddy Family History", 1944 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - "The Crisis in Europe", 1947 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - "Two Encounters with Bigotry and Race Prejudice", 1947 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - "Our China Policy", 1948 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - "The Unfinished Revolution in China", 1948 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - "What Next in China?", 1948 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - "Civil War in China", 1948 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - "The New Japan", 1948 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - "The New Korea", 1948 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - "Divided Korea", 1948 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - "The New Indian Republic", 1949 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - "Pakistan and Turkey", 1949 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - "The Problems of India", 1949 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - "Religion and Politics in India", 1949 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - "The Story of Herbert Kim", 1949 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - "Pakistan and Turkey", 1949 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - "China in Distress", 1949 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - "What About Formosa", 1950 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - "Why Repeat Our Mistakes in Asia?", 1951 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - "Tito and the Archbishop", 1952 (Box 6, Folder 126)